Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ annagasparyan17 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership
Creativity Skills
Promotional Marketing

Languages

Armenian (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Full Professional)

Honors-Awards

The Leadership Award Raymond and Editha Edwards Scholarship

Anna Gasparyan

Berkeley Alumna | Marketing • Communications • Social Media Glendale, California, United States

Summary

UC Berkeley alumna, all-things digital, social media management, communications.

As a creative with a head halfway in the clouds, but feet deeply rooted to the ground I recognize beauty in everything and have experience using digital and traditional channels to broadcast feeling and reality to thousands of eyeballs.

Experience

Armenian National Committee of America - Western Region Media and Communications Coordinator January 2023 - August 2023 (8 months)

Los Angeles, California, United States

Managed all aspects of media relations for the organization, from developing marketing campaigns, cultivating key relationships with media personnel, to writing news releases and advisories disseminated to thousands of media publications across the country.

Created rich and creative written copy and visual graphics optimized for search engines, social media, and print brochures, flyers, banners, and step-and-repeats for the largest Armenian American grassroots organization in the western United States.

Successfully promoted dozens of sold-out community events, fundraisers, and luncheons through publication ads, mass newsletters, organically on social media, and leveraging strategically boosted posts on Facebook and Instagram to nearly 50,000 followers across platforms.

Supervised and directed a team of three media and communications interns who created new social media accounts, technical guides, and engaging video content for the organization in their first month alone.

Executed holistic marketing strategy to involve and effectively engage the youth with the organization's mission and activities while simultaneously promoting the internship program which received a record number of applicants since its conception.

AMGtime
Marketing Assistant
March 2022 - January 2023 (11 months)

Glendale, California, United States

- Conducted competitive research to gain insight into payroll software landscape and created master sheet to aid in go-to-market strategy.
- Produced effective marketing collateral, which included pitch decks, press releases, email, display, video, social media posts, and blogs.

Thornbird Marketing
Marketing Intern
April 2022 - November 2022 (8 months)
Remote

- Wrote press releases, blogs, articles, and newsletters for various clients of different industries, including health, tech, and non-profit.
- Created social media content in the form of static posts, stories, flyers,
 videos, animated shorts for clients with varying needs and specific guidelines.

Paneros Clothing Social Media Marketing Intern July 2021 - November 2021 (5 months) Remote

- Used platforms such as Canva, InShot, and Adobe Photoshop to create effective Instagram and Facebook posts and stories, campaign launch videos, and video and static ads.
- Assisted during campaign photoshoots by capturing behind the scenes photography and videography and transformed raw footage into visually appealing branding tools.
- Worked closely with managers to determine social media strategy, ad demographic, and target audience to create an effective ad campaign with limited budget.

Bravo Learning Center Tutor September 2020 - July 2021 (11 months) Glendale, California, United States Aided three high school and two middle school students to raising failing grades into passing ones by using learning and focusing strategies and communicating outside of tutoring hours to gauge progress.

Created weekly staff schedules while maintaining county health guidelines in order to harbor a safe and clean office space for students during the Covid-19 crisis.

Environmental Design Library Circulation Assistant August 2019 - March 2020 (8 months)

Berkeley, California, United States

Handled check-in and check-out process of library books and materials at circulation desk. Communicated with staff, managers, and external librarians to report collected library traffic data.

The Committee for Armenian Students in Public Schools Tutor

November 2018 - June 2019 (8 months)

Glendale, California, United States

Observed and monitored students' behavior and relationship with school subjects to motivate and encourage academic growth. Tracking learning progress in order to identify opportunities to enhance tutoring methods and show growth. Initiated five-minute games at beginning of sessions to inspire and excite students to learn and excel.

Dr. Manvel Mazmanyan, MD. Medical Receptionist February 2018 - November 2018 (10 months)

Glendale, California, United States

Documented patient medical information, case histories and insurance details to facilitate smooth appointments and payment processing. Suggested and implemented the switch from twenty-year-old physical files to a digital patient record system.

Starbucks

Barista

November 2017 - February 2018 (4 months)

Glendale, California, United States

Pleasantly interacting with customers during hectic periods to promote fun, positive environment. Preparing coffee and specialty drinks, cleaning dining

areas, opening register and carrying out other opening and closing duties for the highest grossing Starbucks location at the time.

GLENDALE DIAGNOSTIC IMAGING NETWORK, INC.

Medical Records Clerk
June 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 6 months)

Glendale, California, United States

Acted as a liaison between litigation, copy services, and the radiology facility to manage and create hard-copy medical documentation. Optimized old organizational systems for payment collections, AP/AR, deposits and record-keeping, and created instructional video and literature for future employees. Strictly followed and implemented HIPAA law in order to protect sensitive patient information.

Education

University of California, Berkeley
Bachelor of Science - BS, Business Administration · (2019 - 2021)

Glendale Community College

Associate of Science (AS-T) , Business Administration · (2017 - 2019)